Health and Nutrition Letter UP061
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Health and Nutrition Letter
1997 -- 2021
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Jean Mayer USDA Human Nutrition Research Center on Aging
UP061
0.75 Linear Feet
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Biographical / Historical
The Tufts USDA Human Nutrition Research Center was renamed in honor of former Tufts President, Dr. Jean Mayer, in 1994. The HNRC is operated by Tufts University under the authority of the USDA as a government-owned, contractor-operated facility. The HNRC, situated in downtown Boston on the Tufts Health Sciences campus, opened officially in November 1982.
The HNRC was founded through the advocacy of Jean Mayer, Tufts president and renowned nutritionist. The center's placement in New England was chosen because the large population of older citizens, the variety of ethnic and economic groups, and its urban/rural character make it a microcosm of the US as a whole.
The HNRC is located on the corner of Stuart and Washington Streets on the Boston campus in a building constructed to house the center in 1982. The building was designed by Shepley, Bulfinch, Richardson, and Abbott, and was dedicated in November 5, 1982. Prior to that time the center's activities were housed elsewhere on the Boston campus.
Related Materials
UP081, Tufts University Diet and Nutrition Letter, DCA
Scope and Contents
This collection contains Tufts University's Health and Nutrition Letter which has articles on a variety of health care issues. Previously published under the name Tufts University Diet and Nutrition Letter (UP081), the Health and Nutrition Letter is published by the Jean Mayer USDA Human Nutrition Research Center on Aging. The name change occurred in honor of the publication's 15th anniversary in February 1997. Volumes run March through February.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
- Health and Nutrition Letter, 1997 -- 2021; UP061.001; 0.75 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains issues of the Health and Nutrition Letter, previously published under the name Diet and Nutrition Letter. The Health and Nutrition Letter is published by the Jean Mayer USDA Human Nutrition Research Center on Aging.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Health and Nutrition Letter, Volumes 14-16, 1997 -- 1999; UP061.001.001
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, February, 1997; UP061.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
      Volume, issue
      14, 12
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, March, 1997; UP061.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
      15, 1
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, April, 1997; UP061.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
      15, 2
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, May, 1997; UP061.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
      15, 3
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, June, 1997; UP061.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
      15, 4
    - Health and Nutrition, July, 1997; UP061.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
      15, 5
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, September, 1997; UP061.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
      15, 7
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, November, 1997; UP061.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
      15, 9
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, December, 1997; UP061.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
      15, 10
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, January, 1998; UP061.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
      15, 11
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, February, 1998; UP061.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
      15, 12
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, March, 1998; UP061.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
      16, 1
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, April, 1998; UP061.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
      16, 2
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, May, 1998; UP061.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
      16, 3
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, June, 1998; UP061.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
      16, 4
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, July, 1998; UP061.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
      16, 5
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, August, 1998; UP061.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
      16, 6
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, September, 1998; UP061.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
      16, 7
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, October, 1998; UP061.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
      16, 8
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, November, 1998; UP061.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
      16, 9
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, December, 1998; UP061.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
      16, 10
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, January, 1999; UP061.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
      16, 11
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, February, 1999; UP061.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
      16, 12
  - Health and Nutrition Letter, Volumes 17-18, 1999 -- 2001; UP061.001.002
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, March, 1999; UP061.002.002.00001 (Box 2)
      17, 1
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, April, 1999; UP061.002.002.00002 (Box 2)
      17, 2
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, May, 1999; UP061.002.002.00003 (Box 2)
      17, 3
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, June, 1999; UP061.002.002.00004 (Box 2)
      17, 4
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, July, 1999; UP061.002.002.00005 (Box 2)
      17, 5
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, August, 1999; UP061.002.002.00006 (Box 2)
      17, 6
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, October, 1999; UP061.002.002.00007 (Box 2)
      17, 8
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, November, 1999; UP061.002.002.00008 (Box 2)
      17, 9
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, December, 1999; UP061.002.002.00009 (Box 2)
      17, 10
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, 1999 Annual Index, UP061.002.002.00010 (Box 2)
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, January, 2000; UP061.002.002.00011 (Box 2)
      17, 11
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, February, 2000; UP061.002.002.00012 (Box 2)
      17, 12
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, March, 2000; UP061.002.002.00013 (Box 2)
      18, 1
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, April, 2000; UP061.002.002.00014 (Box 2)
      18, 2
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, June, 2000; UP061.002.002.00015 (Box 2)
      18, 4
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, July, 2000; UP061.002.002.00016 (Box 2)
      18, 5
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, August, 2000; UP061.002.002.00017 (Box 2)
      18, 6
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, September, 2000; UP061.002.002.00018 (Box 2)
      18, 7
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, October, 2000; UP061.002.002.00019 (Box 2)
      18, 8
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, November, 2000; UP061.002.002.00020 (Box 2)
      18, 9
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, December, 2000; UP061.002.002.00021 (Box 2)
      18, 10
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, January, 2001; UP061.002.002.00022 (Box 2)
      18, 11
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, February, 2001; UP061.002.002.00023 (Box 2)
      18, 12
    - Health and Nutrition Annual Index, 2000; UP061.002.002.00024 (Box 2)
  - Health and Nutrition Letter, Volumes 19-20, 2001 -- 2003; UP061.001.003
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, March, 2001; UP061.003.003.00001 (Box 3)
      19, 1
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, April, 2001; UP061.003.003.00002 (Box 3)
      19, 2
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, May, 2001; UP061.003.003.00003 (Box 3)
      19, 3
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, June, 2001; UP061.003.003.00004 (Box 3)
      19, 4
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, July, 2001; UP061.003.003.00005 (Box 3)
      19, 5
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, August, 2001; UP061.003.003.00006 (Box 3)
      19, 6
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, September, 2001; UP061.003.003.00007 (Box 3)
      19, 7
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, October 2001; UP061.001.006.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6)
      Volume, Number
      19, 8
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, November, 2001; UP061.003.003.00008 (Box 3)
      19, 9
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, December, 2001; UP061.003.003.00009 (Box 3)
      19, 10
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, January, 2002; UP061.003.003.00010 (Box 3)
      19, 11
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, February, 2002; UP061.003.003.00011 (Box 3)
      19, 12
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, 2001 Annual Index, UP061.003.003.00012 (Box 3)
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, March, 2002; UP061.003.003.00013 (Box 3)
      20, 1
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, April, 2002; UP061.003.003.00014 (Box 3)
      20, 2
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, May, 2002; UP061.003.003.00015 (Box 3)
      20, 3
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, June, 2002; UP061.003.003.00016 (Box 3)
      20, 4
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, July, 2002; UP061.003.003.00017 (Box 3)
      20, 5
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, August, 2002; UP061.003.003.00018 (Box 3)
      20, 6
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, September, 2002; UP061.003.003.00019 (Box 3)
      20, 7
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, October, 2002; UP061.003.003.00020 (Box 3)
      20, 8
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, November, 2002; UP061.003.003.00021 (Box 3)
      20, 9
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, January, 2003; UP061.003.003.00022 (Box 3)
      20, 11
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, February, 2003; UP061.003.003.00023 (Box 3)
      20, 12
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, 2002 Annual Index, UP061.003.003.00024 (Box 3)
  - Health and Nutrition Letter, Volumes 21-26, 2003 -- 2009; UP061.001.004
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, March, 2003; UP061.004.004.00001 (Box 4)
      21, 1
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, April, 2003; UP061.004.004.00002 (Box 4)
      21, 2
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, May, 2003; UP061.004.004.00003 (Box 4)
      21, 3
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, June, 2003; UP061.004.004.00004 (Box 4)
      21, 4
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, July 2003; UP061.001.006.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6)
      21, 5
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, August 2003; UP061.001.006.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6)
      21, 6
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, September, 2003; UP061.004.004.00005 (Box 4)
      21, 7
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, October 2003; UP061.001.006.00004 (Box 6)
      21, 8
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, November 2003; UP061.001.006.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6)
      21, 9
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, December 2003; UP061.001.006.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6)
      21, 10
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, January 2004; UP061.001.006.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6)
      21, 11
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, February, 2004; UP061.004.004.00006 (Box 4)
      21, 12
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, March, 2004; UP061.004.004.00007 (Box 4)
      22, 1
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, April 2004; UP061.001.006.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6)
      22, 2
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, May 2004; UP061.001.006.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6)
      22, 3
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, June 2004; UP061.001.006.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6)
      22, 4
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, July, 2004; UP061.004.004.00008 (Box 4)
      22, 5
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, August, 2004; UP061.004.004.00009 (Box 4)
      22, 6
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, September, 2004; UP061.004.004.00010 (Box 4)
      22, 7
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, October, 2004; UP061.004.004.00011 (Box 4)
      22, 8
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, November, 2004; UP061.004.004.00012 (Box 4)
      22, 9
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, December, 2004; UP061.004.004.00013 (Box 4)
      22, 10
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, January, 2005; UP061.004.004.00014 (Box 4)
      22, 11
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, February, 2005; UP061.004.004.00015 (Box 4)
      22, 12
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, March, 2005; UP061.004.004.00016 (Box 4)
      23, 1
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, April, 2005; UP061.004.004.00017 (Box 4)
      23, 2
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, May, 2005; UP061.004.004.00018 (Box 4)
      23, 3
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, June, 2005; UP061.004.004.00019 (Box 4)
      23, 4
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, July, 2005; UP061.004.004.00020 (Box 4)
      23, 5
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, August, 2005; UP061.004.004.00021 (Box 4)
      23, 6
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, September 2005; UP061.001.006.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6)
      23, 7
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, October, 2005; UP061.004.004.00022 (Box 4)
      23, 8
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, November, 2005; UP061.004.004.00023 (Box 4)
      23, 9
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, December, 2005; UP061.004.004.00024 (Box 4)
      23, 10
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, January, 2006; UP061.004.004.00025 (Box 4)
      23, 11
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, February, 2006; UP061.004.004.00026 (Box 4)
      23, 12
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, March, 2006; UP061.004.004.00027 (Box 4)
      24, 1
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, April, 2006; UP061.004.004.00028 (Box 4)
      24, 2
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, May, 2006; UP061.004.004.00029 (Box 4)
      24, 3
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, June, 2006; UP061.004.004.00030 (Box 4)
      24, 4
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, July, 2006; UP061.004.004.00031 (Box 4)
      24, 5
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, August, 2006; UP061.004.004.00032 (Box 4)
      24, 6
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, September, 2006; UP061.004.004.00033 (Box 4)
      24, 7
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, October, 2006; UP061.004.004.00034 (Box 4)
      [8]
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, November, 2006; UP061.004.004.00035 (Box 4)
      [9]
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, December, 2006; UP061.004.004.00036 (Box 4)
      [10]
      24, 8
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, January, 2007; UP061.004.004.00037 (Box 4)
      [11]
      24, 9
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, February, 2007; UP061.004.004.00038 (Box 4)
      24, 12
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, March, 2007; UP061.004.004.00039 (Box 4)
      25, 1
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, April, 2007; UP061.004.004.00040 (Box 4)
      25, 2
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, May, 2007; UP061.004.004.00041 (Box 4)
      25, 3
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, June, 2007; UP061.004.004.00042 (Box 4)
      25, 4
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, July, 2007; UP061.004.004.00043 (Box 4)
      25, 5
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, August, 2007; UP061.004.004.00044 (Box 4)
      25, 6
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, September, 2007; UP061.004.004.00045 (Box 4)
      25, 7
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, October, 2007; UP061.004.004.00046 (Box 4)
      25, 8
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, November, 2007; UP061.004.004.00047 (Box 4)
      25, 9
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, December, 2007; UP061.004.004.00048 (Box 4)
      25, 10
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, January, 2008; UP061.004.004.00049 (Box 4)
      25, 11
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, February, 2008; UP061.004.004.00050 (Box 4)
      25, 12
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, March, 2008; UP061.004.004.00051 (Box 4)
      26, 1
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, April, 2008; UP061.004.004.00052 (Box 4)
      26, 2
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, May, 2008; UP061.004.004.00053 (Box 4)
      26, 3
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, June, 2008; UP061.004.004.00054 (Box 4)
      26, 4
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, July, 2008; UP061.004.004.00055 (Box 4)
      26, 5
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, August, 2008; UP061.004.004.00056 (Box 4)
      26, 6
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, September, 2008; UP061.004.004.00057 (Box 4)
      26, 7
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, October, 2008; UP061.004.004.00058 (Box 4)
      26, 8
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, November, 2008; UP061.004.004.00059 (Box 4)
      26, 9
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, December, 2008; UP061.004.004.00060 (Box 4)
      26, 10
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, January, 2009; UP061.004.004.00061 (Box 4)
      26, 11
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, February, 2009; UP061.004.004.00062; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy (Box 4)
      26, 12
  - Health and Nutrition Letter, Volumes 27-37, 2009 -- 2021; UP061.001.005
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, March, 2009; UP061.005.005.00001; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy (Box 5)
      27, 1
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, April, 2009; UP061.005.005.00002; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy (Box 5)
      27, 2
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, May, 2009; UP061.005.005.00003; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy (Box 5)
      27, 3
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, June, 2009; UP061.005.005.00004; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy (Box 5)
      27, 4
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, July, 2009; UP061.005.005.00005; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy (Box 5)
      27, 5
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, August, 2009; UP061.005.005.00006; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy (Box 5)
      27, 6
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, September, 2009; UP061.005.005.00007; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy (Box 5)
      27, 7
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, October, 2009; UP061.005.005.00008; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy (Box 5)
      27, 8
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, November, 2009; UP061.005.005.00009; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy (Box 5)
      27, 9
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, December, 2009; UP061.005.005.00010; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy (Box 5)
      27, 10
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, January, 2010; UP061.005.005.00011; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy (Box 5)
      27, 11
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, February, 2010; UP061.005.005.00012; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy (Box 5)
      27, 12
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, March, 2010; UP061.005.005.00013; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy (Box 5)
      28, 1
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, April, 2010; UP061.005.005.00014; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy (Box 5)
      28, 2
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, May, 2010; UP061.005.005.00015 (Box 5)
      28, 3
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, June, 2010; UP061.005.005.00016 (Box 5)
      28, 4
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, July, 2010; UP061.005.005.00017 (Box 5)
      28, 5
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, August, 2010; UP061.005.005.00018 (Box 5)
      28, 6
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, September, 2010; UP061.005.005.00019 (Box 5)
      28, 7
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, October, 2010; UP061.005.005.00020 (Box 5)
      28, 8
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, November, 2010; UP061.005.005.00021 (Box 5)
      28, 9
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, December, 2010; UP061.005.005.00022 (Box 5)
      28, 10
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, January, 2011; UP061.005.005.00023 (Box 5)
      28, 11
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, February, 2011; UP061.005.005.00024 (Box 5)
      28, 12
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, March, 2011; UP061.005.005.00025 (Box 5)
      29, 1
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, April, 2011; UP061.005.005.00026 (Box 5)
      29, 2
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, May, 2011; UP061.005.005.00027 (Box 5)
      29, 3
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, June, 2011; UP061.005.005.00028 (Box 5)
      29, 4
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, July, 2011; UP061.005.005.00029 (Box 5)
      29, 5
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, August, 2011; UP061.005.005.00030 (Box 5)
      29, 6
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, September, 2011; UP061.005.005.00031 (Box 5)
      29, 7
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, October, 2011; UP061.005.005.00032 (Box 5)
      29, 8
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, November, 2011; UP061.005.005.00033 (Box 5)
      29, 9
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, December, 2011; UP061.005.005.00034 (Box 5)
      29, 10
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, January, 2012; UP061.005.005.00035 (Box 5)
      29, 11
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, February, 2012; UP061.005.005.00036 (Box 5)
      29, 12
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, March, 2012; UP061.005.005.00037 (Box 5)
      30, 1
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, April, 2012; UP061.005.005.00038 (Box 5)
      30, 2
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, May, 2012; UP061.005.005.00039 (Box 5)
      30, 3
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, June, 2012; UP061.005.005.00040 (Box 5)
      30, 4
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, July, 2012; UP061.005.005.00041 (Box 5)
      30, 5
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, August, 2012; UP061.005.005.00042 (Box 5)
      30, 6
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, September, 2012; UP061.005.005.00043 (Box 5)
      30, 7
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, October, 2012; UP061.005.005.00044 (Box 5)
      30, 8
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, November, 2012; UP061.005.005.00045 (Box 5)
      30, 9
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, December, 2012; UP061.005.005.00046 (Box 5)
      30, 10
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, January, 2013; UP061.005.005.00047 (Box 5)
      30, 11
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, February, 2013; UP061.005.005.00048 (Box 5)
      30, 12
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, March, 2013; UP061.005.005.00049 (Box 5)
      31, 1
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, April, 2013; UP061.005.005.00050 (Box 5)
      31, 2
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, May, 2013; UP061.005.005.00051 (Box 5)
      31, 3
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, June, 2013; UP061.005.005.00052 (Box 5)
      31, 4
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, July, 2013; UP061.005.005.00053 (Box 5)
      31, 5
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, September, 2013; UP061.005.005.00054 (Box 5)
      31, 7
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, October, 2013; UP061.005.005.00055 (Box 5)
      31, 8
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, November, 2013; UP061.005.005.00056 (Box 5)
      31, 9
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, December, 2013; UP061.005.005.00057 (Box 5)
      31, 10
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, January, 2014; UP061.005.005.00058 (Box 5)
      31, 11
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, February, 2014; UP061.005.005.00059 (Box 5)
      31, 12
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, March, 2014; UP061.005.005.00060 (Box 5)
      32, 1
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, April, 2014; UP061.005.005.00061 (Box 5)
      32, 2
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, May, 2014; UP061.005.005.00062 (Box 5)
      32, 3
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, June, 2014; UP061.005.005.00063 (Box 5)
      32, 4
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, August, 2014; UP061.005.005.00064 (Box 5)
      32, 6
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, September, 2014; UP061.005.005.00065 (Box 5)
      32, 7
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, October, 2014; UP061.005.005.00066 (Box 5)
      32, 8
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, November, 2014; UP061.005.005.00067 (Box 5)
      32, 9
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, December, 2014; UP061.005.005.00068 (Box 5)
      32, 10
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, January, 2015; UP061.005.005.00069 (Box 5)
      32, 11
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, February, 2015; UP061.005.005.00070 (Box 5)
      32, 12
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, March, 2015; UP061.005.005.00071 (Box 5)
      33, 01
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, May, 2015; UP061.005.005.00072 (Box 5)
      33, 03
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, June, 2015; UP061.005.005.00073 (Box 5)
      33, 04
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, July, 2015; UP061.005.005.00074 (Box 5)
      33, 05
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, August, 2015; UP061.005.005.00075 (Box 5)
      33, 06
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, September, 2015; UP061.005.005.00076 (Box 5)
      33, 07
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, October, 2015; UP061.005.005.00077 (Box 5)
      33, 08
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, June 2016; UP061.001.006.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6)
      34, 4
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, August 2016; UP061.001.006.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6)
      34, 6
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, October 2016; UP061.001.006.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6)
      34, 8
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, January 2018; UP061.001.006.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6)
      35, 11
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, June 2018; UP061.001.006.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6)
      36, 4
    - Health and Nutrition Letter, October 2018; UP061.001.006.00018 (Box 6)